<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Reducing Gas Sensor Monitor</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="menu_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_sensordrone_control">Reducing Gas Sensor Monitor</string>
    
    <string name="intro">To connect, touch connect from the menu.  Once you are connected, your Sensordrone will flash blue.  To graph, touch the numeric readout for the sensor.</string>
    
    <string name="title1">Reducing Gases</string>
    <string name="description1">The reducing gas sensor will show strong responses to reducing gases.  Reducing gases include most fuels like propane, butane and many other hydrocarbons, volatile organic compounds (VOCs) like alcohols, hydrogen, carbon monoxide, hydrogen sulfide, etc.  The resistance of the reducing gas sensor will decrease proportional to the reducing gas concentration (logarithmic response).</string>

     <string name="title2">Oxidizing Gases</string>
    <string name="description2">The oxidizing gas sensor will show strong responses to oxidizing.  Oxidizing gases include strong oxidizing agents like ozone, nitrogen dioxide, chlorine and fluorine, etc.  The resistance of the reducing gas sensor will increase proportional to the oxidizing gas concentration (logarithmic response).</string>
    
    <string name="title3">General Information</string>
    <string name="description3">This app returns unconditioned resistance data from the Sensordrone’s reducing gas sensor.  This sensors uses large amounts of power and can take significant time to stabilize.  This app is mainly meant as an introduction to these sensors for developers and users.  The best way to use this app is to turn on the sensor and tap the number to graph.  Once the graph is fairly stable, you can look for leaks/gas sources, which can cause a large resistance change.</string>
    
    <string name="warning">Ensure your Sensordrone is fully charged before using this app.  The reducing gas sensor uses a significant amount of power, and is best used as a relative sensor (e.g. a leak detector), that is, to detect changes in signal.  Developers should take this into account if they use this sensor in an app. This sensor will cause the Sensordrone to self heat while on.</string>
</resources>